Joseph Sciorra collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2. Italian American religious expression and material culture, ca. 1974-2017
  - Subseries 1. Shrines, domestic altars, and grottos, ca. 1981-2013
    - Sub-subseries 1: Black Madonna (Madonna Nera), ca. 1989-2006
      - Black Madonna exhibit notes (general), 1999-2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 21/7)
      - Black Madonna general, 1998-2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 21/8)
      - Black Madonna lecture, 2002-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 21/9)
      - Black Madonna Lucia Chianola Birnbaum tour of Sicily, 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 21/10)
      - Black Madonna negatives, Romeo, ca. 1998, AFC 2018/065: PH108; 4 film negatives, black and white (35mm) (Box 63)
      - Black Madonna Pre Christian research, ca. 1997-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 21/11)
      - Black Madonna talk, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 21/12)
      - Black Madonna Tindari, ca. 1989-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 21/13)
      - David Roediger - Giuliano and Black Madonna, 2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 21/14)
      - East 13th St. Black Madonna photos, ca. 2004-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts with 5 color photographic prints (4x6) and 1 photographic print, black and white (8x10) (Box-folder 21/15)
      - East 13th WPA, 1999-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 21/16)
      - Exhibit drafts, 2000, 1 folder of manuscripts with 16 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 21/17)
      - Exhibit drafts, 2000, AFC 2018/065: PH109; 32 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 63)
      - Genesis II Museum of International Black Culture, 2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 21/18)
      - Italian American images, 1992-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 22/1)
      - Madonna Nera - New York City, 1999-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 22/2)
      - Madonna Nera Hoboken, 2000-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts with 8 photographic prints (4x6) (Box-folder 22/3)
      - Madonna Nera Hoboken, 2000-2001, AFC 2018/065: PH105; 10 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 63)
      - Madonna Nera I Giullari, 1992-1994, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 22/4)
      - Madonna Nera in Italy, 1/2, 2000-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 22/5)
      - Madonna Nera in Italy, 2/2, 2000-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 22/6)
      - Personal altar, Stephanie Romeo, ca. 1998-1999, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 22/7)
      - Sal Salerno presentation, 1995, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 22/8)
      - Suitcase, personal altar photographs, 1/2, ca. 1998, 1 folder of manuscripts with 37 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 22/9)
      - Suitcase, personal altar photographs, 1/2, ca. 1998, AFC 2018/065: PH106; 62 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 63)
      - Suitcase, personal altar photographs, 2/2, ca. 1998, 1 folder of manuscripts with 10 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 22/10)
      - Suitcase, personal altar photographs, 2/2, ca. 1998, AFC 2018/065: PH107; 36 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 63)
      - Tommi Avicolli Mecca play, 2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 22/11)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Presepio, ca. 1982-2014
      Research and documentation of the presepio (nativity scene) tradition.
      - Alfonso Magliulo interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 22/12)
      - Camillo "David" Greco interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 22/13)
      - Chris DeVito interview, 1989-1990, 2002, 2002, 1 folder of manuscripts with 20 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 22/14)
      - Chris DeVito, Presepio, December 31, 2002, AFC 2018/065: SR173; 1 sound cassette: analog
      - Christmas, Calabria, 1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 22/15)
      - Day after Presepio, 1984-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts with 4 photographic prints, color (3.5x5) (Box-folder 22/16)
      - Day after Presepio, 1984-1990, AFC 2018/065: PH015; 16 slides, color (35 mm) (Box 49)
      - Dolly interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 22/17)
      - F. and G. Lanzi: Il Presepe (book excerpt), 2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 22/18)
      - Fabio Flaim interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 22/19)
      - Flora and Enzo Simeone interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts with 2 photographic prints, color (polaroid, 3.5x4.5) (Box-folder 22/20)
      - Flora and Enzo Simeone interview, 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: PH024; 47 slides, color (35mm) (Box 49-50)
      - Francesco Ventura interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts with 1 photographic print, color (polaroid, 3.5x4.5) (Box-folder 22/21)
      - Francesco Ventura interview, 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: PH023; 3 slides, color (35mm) (Box 49)
      - Frank and Frances Vigliarolo interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/1)
      - Frank De Bernardo interview, 1989, 2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/2)
      - Frank De Bernardo interview, 1989, 2000, AFC 2018/065: PH016; 29 slides, color (35 mm) (Box 49)
      - Frank Guido interview, 1989, AFC 2018/065: PH018; 3 slides, color (35 mm) (Box 49)
      - Frank Guido interview, 1989, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/3)
      - Garry Wills article (Art and Politics of the Nativity), 1996, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/4)
      - Giovanni Miniero, ca. 1998, 1 folder of manuscripts with 6 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 23/5)
      - Giuseppe Monfoletto interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts with 2 photographic prints, color (polaroid, 3.5x4.5) (Box-folder 23/6)
      - Giuseppe Monfoletto interview, 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: PH019; 21 slides, color (35mm) (Box 49)
      - Iachetta family interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/7)
      - Iachetta family interview, 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: PH027; 14 slides, color (35 mm) (Box 50)
      - Il Presepi traditions outside NYC, ca. 2002-2012, 1 folder of manuscripts with 10 photographic prints, color (4x6 and smaller) (Box-folder 23/8)
      - Il Presepio (book), 1992, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/9)
      - Joe Gaeta interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/10)
      - John Greco, Holy Land, 1988-2013, AFC 2018/065: PH098; 70 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 62)
      - John Greco, Holy Land, 1988-2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/11)
      - John Greco, Holy Land, 1988-2013, 1 folder of manuscripts with 38 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 23/12)
      - Joseph Furnari interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts with 1 photographic print, color (polaroid, 3.5x4.5) (Box-folder 23/13)
      - Joseph Furnari interview, 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: PH025; 13 slides, color (35mm) (Box 50)
      - Joseph Giarrusso interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/14)
      - Laccitello - Daily News, 1997, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/15)
      - Maria Saraceni interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts with 1 photographic print, color (polaroid, 3.5x4.5) (Box-folder 23/16)
      - Maria Saraceni interview, 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: PH022; 5 slides, color (35mm) (Box 49)
      - Mike Pensini interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/17)
      - Mike Pensini interview, 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: PH021; 4 slides, color (35mm) (Box 49)
      - Mike's Pizza, ca. 2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/18)
      - Mike's Pizza, ca. 2000, AFC 2018/065: PH026; 9 slides, color (Box 50)
      - Miscellaneous grant narration, ca. 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/19)
      - Mola di Bari, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/20)
      - My New York Presepio, 2001-2008, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 45/9)
      - NEA Folk Arts grant application, 1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/21)
      - NEA Folk Arts grant application materials, 1988-1989, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/22)
        Photos by Lillian Caruana
      - New Jersey Parquinelle (?) Di Miglio, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts with 8 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 23/23)
      - New Jersey Parquinelle (?) Di Miglio, undated, AFC 2018/065: PH017; 25 slides, color (35mm) (Box 49)
      - New York State Council (NYSCA) II Presepio project planning and development, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/24)
      - New York State Council on the Arts (NYSCA) application, 1989, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 23/25)
      - New York State Council on the Arts (NYSCA) proposal, 1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/1)
      - Official Presepio presentations, 1983-2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/2)
      - Peter Lurito interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/3)
      - Philadelphia Presepio maker, figure marker; Flavinno Gloria with daughter Mary Gloria and Dorothy Marcuca. Interviewer, Joseph Sciorra., February 2, 1987, AFC 2018/065: SR172; 1 sound cassette: analog
      - Piana Carnizzo, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/4)
      - Political Presepi, Italy, 2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/5)
      - POW Presepio, California, 2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/6)
      - Presepi article and panel, Sciorra, 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/7)
      - Presepi in New York City, 2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/8)
      - Presepi lectures, 2002-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/9)
      - Presepio article, ca. 2001-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (legal) (Box-folder 45/8)
      - Presepio articles (general), 1963-2008, 1 folder of manuscripts (legal) (Box-folder 45/11)
      - Presepio bibliography, ca. 2000-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/10)
      - Presepio correspondence, 1989-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts with 8 photographic prints, color (4x6 inch) (Box-folder 24/11)
      - Presepio folklore articles, ca. 2008, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/12)
      - Presepio images, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/13)
      - Presepio in New York, 1982-2014, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/14)
      - Presepio poems, 1998-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/15)
      - Presepio project publicity, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/16)
      - Presepio slides, undated, AFC 2018/065: PH014; 1 slide, color (35 mm) (Box 49)
      - Presepio talk, Buffalo, 1992-1997, 1 folder of manuscripts (legal) (Box-folder 45/7)
      - Presepio Vivente - in Queens, 1986-1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/17)
      - Presepio, Sicily, 1979-2012, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/18)
      - Presepio, tape 1. Camillo Greco, Nov. 25, 1989; Frank Di Bernardo., 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: SR162; 1 sound cassette: analog
      - Presepio, tape 2. Camillo Greco, Nov. 25, 1989; Flora and Enzo Simeone, part 1, December 6, 1989; Guiseppe Monfoletto, part 1, December 6, 1989., 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: SR163; 1 sound cassette: analog
      - Presepio, tape 3. Flora and Enzo Simeone, part 2, December 6, 1989; Guiseppe Monfoletto, December 6, 1989; Natale and Isabella Rotondi, December 7, 1989., 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: SR164; 1 sound cassette: analog
      - Presepio, tape 4. Joseph and Gasper Furnari, December 7, 1989; Maria Sarcceni, December 8, 1989, 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: SR165; 1 sound cassette: analog
      - Presepio, tape 5. Mary Natuzzi with Rev. Dominic Adessa, December 8, 1989; Rev. John Starace and Salvatore "Teddy" Starace, December 10, 1989., 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: SR166; 1 sound cassette: analog
      - Presepio, tape 6. Joey Dente, December 11, 1989; Francesco Ventura, December 13, 1989., 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: SR167; 1 sound cassette: analog
      - Presepio, tape 7. Lorraine Iachetta with mother Assunte, December 10, 1989; Antonio Vigliante, St. Anatoshia (?) (part one), December 21, 1989., 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: SR168; 1 sound cassette: analog
      - Presepio, tape 8. Presepio at St. Mary's Church, Bensonhurst; Vincent Miceli, Gaetano Pagnotta, Antonio Ippolito, December 13, 1989; Mike Panseni with nephew John Garza, December 18, 1989., 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: SR169; 1 sound cassette: analog
      - Presepio, tape 9. Antonio Vigliante, December 21, 1989; Frank Guido, December 5, 1989., 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: SR170; 1 sound cassette: analog
      - Presepio: Natale Rotondi, 1995-2009, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/19)
        - Rotondi Ervoto, afc2018065_dc072; 2 photographs (TIF)
      - Presepio: Natale Rotondi, 1995-2009, AFC 2018/065: PH033; 19 slides, color (35mm) (Box 49)
      - Presepio-like traditions, miscellaneous, 1989-2008, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 24/20)
      - Presepio-Naples, 1967-1995, 1 folder of manuscripts; article by Sciorra (Box-folder 24/21)
      - Presepio-Puglia, 1984-1992, 1 folder of manuscripts; article by Sciorra and photos by Martha Cooper (Box-folder 25/1)
      - Rotondi family interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts with 1 photographic print, color (polaroid, 3.5x4.5) (Box-folder 25/2)
      - Stefania Romano interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 25/3)
      - Teddy and Anna Starace interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts with 2 photographic prints, color (polaroid, 3.5x4.5) (Box-folder 25/4)
      - Tony Vigilante/St. Anthanius Church, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 25/5)
      - Tony Vigilante/St. Anthanius Church, 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: PH028; 19 slides, color (35mm) (Box 50)
      - Various Christmas (nativity) traditions, 1987-2008, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 25/6)
      - Vincent and Elizabeth Pugliano interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 25/7)
      - Vincent Miceli/St. Mary's Church interview, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts with 1 photographic print, color (polaroid, 3.5x4.5) (Box-folder 25/8)
      - Vincent Miceli/St. Mary's Church interview, 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: PH020; 7 slides, color (35mm) (Box 49)
- Series 3. Italian American music, theater, poetry, and visual arts, ca. 1980-2016
  Research and documentation of Italian folk art, poetry, including of the Sicilian poet Vincent Ancona, theater, puppets, as well as music, including Rap, Hip-hop and Doo-wop.
  - Accordion, 2000-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 25/9)
  - Biancheria and Rock & Roll memo and funding report, 2001-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 25/10)
  - A Braver Kind, afc2018065_dc061; 13 audio files (WAV)
  - City Play items (Museum of the City of New York), 1985-1993, 1 folder of manuscripts with 6 photographic prints, color; 2 contact sheets, black and white (Box-folder 25/11)
  - City Play items (Museum of the City of New York), 1985-1993, AFC 2018/065: PH009; 3 slides, color (35mm) (Box 48)
  - City Play items (Museum of the City of New York), 1985-1993, AFC 2018/065: PH094; 48 film negatives, black and white (35mm) (Box 62)
  - Ethnic Folk Arts images, ca. 1980s, AFC 2018/065: PH041; 42 slides, color (35mm) (Box 53)
  - Ethnic Folk Arts images, 1/2, ca. 1980s, 1 folder of manuscripts with 21 photographic prints, black and white (5x7) (Box-folder 25/12)
  - Ethnic Folk Arts images, 2/2, ca. 1980s, 1 folder of manuscripts with 13 photographic prints, black and white (8x10) (Box-folder 25/13)
  - Evviva La Banda, afc2018065_dc044; 14 audio files (WAV)
  - Father and Song: Volume One, afc2018065_dc073; The Faiellas's; 15 audio files (WAV)
  - First Vincenzo Ancona article, 1983-1985, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 25/14)
  - First Vincenzo Ancona grant, Ancona program, 1983-1987, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 25/15)
  - Giuseppe Ancona boats, 1992, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 25/16)
  - Giuseppe Ancona boats, 1992, AFC 2018/065: PH052; 1 slide, color (35 mm) (Box 54)
  - Graffiti, 2004, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 25/17)
  - Graffiti paper, ca. 1997, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 25/18)
  - Hip Hop from the Italian Diaspora 2, 2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 25/19)
  - (Hip Hop from the Italian) Diaspora flyers/press, 1999-2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 25/20)
  - History of theater research, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 25/21)
  - "I Giullari Di Piazza" (theater company) info, 1993-1995, 1 folder of manuscripts with 2 photographic prints, black and white (8x10) (Box-folder 26/1)
  - "I Giullari Di Piazza," budget and debts, 1995-1997, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 26/2)
  - "I Giullari Di Piazza" By-Laws, 1983, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 26/3)
  - "I Giullari Di Piazza" fundraiser flyers, 1/2, 1992-1996, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 26/4)
  - "I Giullari Di Piazza" fundraiser flyers, 2/2, 1992-1996, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 26/5)
  - "I Giullari Di Piazza" letterhead, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 26/6)
  - "I Giullari Di Piazza," Lincoln Center, 1996, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 26/7)
  - "I Giullari Di Piazza" materials, 1992-1995, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 26/8)
  - "I Giullari Di Piazza" minutes and agendas, 1992-1995, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 26/9)
  - "I Giullari Di Piazza" performances, 1991-1992, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 26/10)
  - "I Giullari Di Piazza" programs, 1995-1997, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 26/11)
  - "I Giullari Di Piazza" publicity, ca. 1992, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 26/12)
  - "Addo t'a Pizzicato a Tarantella," 1982, ca. 1982; AFC 2018/065: SR236; 1 sound cassette: analog
    Performer: I Giullari Di Piazza.
  - Sulillo Mio; Southern Italian Folk Music, 1986, ca. 1986; AFC 2018/065: SR237; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Italian American Folk Art exhibit proposal, 2001-2004, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 26/13)
  - Italian American Folk Art exhibition, 1/2, 1999-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 26/14)
  - Italian American Folk Art exhibition, 2/2, 1999-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts with 12 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 26/15)
  - Italian American Folk Art exhibition, 2/2, 1999-2001, AFC 2018/065: PH103; 40 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 63)
  - Italian American Folk Arts slides, 1999-2001, AFC 2018/065: PH034; 12 slides, black and white (35mm); 46 slides, color (35mm) (Box 51)
  - Italian American music/dance, Francis Grasso, 1999-2004, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 27/1)
  - Italian art/poetry: Sicilian poetry - City Lore, 2000-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 27/2)
  - Italian art/poetry: Sicilian poetry "prior press," 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 27/3)
  - Italian art/poetry: Vincent Ancona exhibitions, 1987-1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 27/4)
  - Italian brass bands, 1984-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 27/5)
  - Italian craft traditions in Philadelphia, 1987, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 27/6)
  - Italian Folk Arts survey of Nassau and Queens, 1986, AFC 2018/065: PH082; 22 slides, color (35mm) (Box 59)
  - Italian Folk Arts survey of Nassau and Queens, 1/3, 1986, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 27/7)
  - Italian Folk Arts survey of Nassau and Queens, 2/3, 1986, 1 folder of manuscripts with 1 photographic print, color (4x5) (Box-folder 27/8)
  - Italian Folk Arts survey of Nassau and Queens, 3/3, 1986, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 27/9)
  - Italian folk music, 1/2, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 27/10)
  - Italian folk music, 2/2, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts with 3 photographic prints, black and white (8x10) (Box-folder 27/11)
  - Italian folk music: De Franco family, ca. 1987-1989, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 27/12)
  - Italian folk music: I Giullari di Piazza, ca. 1995, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 27/13)
  - Italian Folk: Vernacular Culture in Italian American Lives reviews, 2011-2016, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 28/1)
  - Italian librettos, 1/4, ca. 1900-1910, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 28/2)
  - Italian librettos, 2/4, ca. 1900-1910, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 28/3)
  - Italian librettos, 3/4, ca. 1900-1910, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 28/4)
  - Italian librettos, 4/4, ca. 1900-1910, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 28/5)
  - Italian music: I Giullari di Piazza, 1992-1996, 1 folder of manuscripts with 1 film negative, black and white (8x10) (Box-folder 28/6)
  - Italian poetry: Italian-American poetry, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 28/7)
  - Italian poetry: Vincent Ancona, 1993-2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 28/8)
  - Italian poetry: Vincent Ancona biography, articles, etc., ca. 1982-2006, 6 photographic prints, black and white (3.5x5) (Box-folder 29/1)
  - Italian poetry: Vincent Ancona biography, articles, etc., ca. 1982-2006, AFC 2018/065: PH122; 5 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 64)
  - Italian poetry: Vincent Ancona poetry, 1/2, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 29/2)
  - Italian poetry: Vincent Ancona poetry, 2/2, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 29/3)
  - Italian poetry: Vincent Ancona research and writing, ca. 1997-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 29/4)
  - Italian songbook: Canzune Nostre, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 29/5)
  - Italian theater (Mola), 1/2, 1979-1987, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 29/6)
  - Italian theater (Mola), 2/2, 1979-1987, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 29/7)
  - Italian theater, music, dance productions, 1995-1997, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 29/8)
  - Italian-American folk arts in Nassau and Queens, ca. 1983-1987, 1 folder of manuscripts with 7 prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 30/1)
  - Italian-American folk arts in Nassau and Queens, ca. 1983-1987, AFC 2018/065: PH013; 2 slides, color (Box 49)
  - Italian-American folk arts in Nassau and Queens, ca. 1983-1987, AFC 2018/065: PH096; 28 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 62)
  - Jibaro Borincano, undated, AFC 2018/065: SR240; 1 sound cassette: analog
    Performer: Jorge Estrada, El Jibarito de Arecibo.
  - Made By Hand - Played By Heart: A Guide to Traditional Arts in Queens, 1991, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 30/2)
  - Malidittu La Lingua (Chairetakis and Sciorra book) reviews, 1990-1995, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 30/3)
  - Manteo presentation, 2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 30/4)
  - Manteo puppets, 2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 30/5)
  - Manteo Sicilian marionette folk theater, ca. 1981-2017, AFC 2018/065: PH035; 8 slides, color (35mm) (Box 51)
  - Manteo Sicilian marionette folk theater, 1/2, ca. 1981-2017, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 30/6)
  - Manteo Sicilian marionette folk theater, 2/2, ca. 1981-2017, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 30/7)
  - Martha Cooper photos of graffiti art around NYC, undated, AFC 2018/065: PH012; 104 slides, color (Box 47-48)
  - National Italian American Foundation (NIAF) grant, 2001-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 30/8)
  - Needlework, 2001-2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 30/9)
  - New Mola theater, 1/2, 1983-1986, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 30/10)
  - New Mola theater, 2/2, 1983-1986, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 31/1)
  - Poetry: Vincenzo Ancona article by Sciorra, 1985, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 31/2)
  - Puppet research, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 31/3)
  - Queens College Rock and Roll symposium, 2001-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 31/4)
  - Religious arts of Italian Americans in NYC, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 31/5)
  - Reweaving the Past (article), 1985, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 31/6)
  - Rhythms and Roots 2015, afc2018065_dc060; Villa Palagonia; 13 audio files (WAV)
  - Rock & Roll/Doo-wop, 2000-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 31/7)
  - Rock and Roll symposium, invitation letter, 2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 31/8)